And now we welcome in the newest member
of the New York Football Giants with the
10th overall pick in the 2026 NFL Draft,
the New York Giants selected CC Mau Noa,
offensive lineman out of the University
of Miami. CC, man, I can only imagine
how excited he is to hear his name get
called on that stage. What are you most
excited about coming to the New York
Football Giants? Man, getting to serve
my teammates, man. Getting to get it
going and get getting to compete and
have fun with the team, man. What was
your experience like throughout this
process with the Giants talking to John
Harbaugh, Joe Schoen, and the coaching
staff? Man, I built a great uh
foundation with Coach Bloom, man. I love
that guy to death. And uh
when I got that call, man, I I just
can't wait to get to work right now,
bro. You play with a certain amount of
attitude on the offensive line. How
would you describe your playing style to
Giant fans that maybe haven't seen you
play a ton of football? You got to, man.
You got to play with attitude. That's
that's the way that football is meant to
be. You got to play with attitude. You
got to play with with uh urgency. And
you know, at this level uh at the NFL
level, man,
you know, people are gunning for your
job. So,
I'm going to make sure that I do
whatever it takes to take care of my
family. What is your goal and what is
your mindset in terms of protecting
Jackson Dart, but also trying to move
people in the run game? Oh, protecting
Jackson Dart is priority one. He's a key
principle of the offense. We just keep
him protected and he's going to do his
own thing.
Uh run game, man, we just got to open up
the hole and let Scat back do his thing.
It's as simple as that. Definition of
blocking, moving somebody from point A
to point B against his will. I love to
hear it. You come from a football
family. Uh you have two older brothers.
One went to Washington State, was a
center. He was in the league for a bit.
And your brother, Francisco, plays for
the Jets. How did they help you prepare
for this process and and kind of get you
to where you are today? Man, they helped
me a lot, man. With with Francisco, he
uh plays for the New York Jets, so next
door neighbor. We yeah, we've been
talking about it, man. Get ready for for
fall camp, man. I'm coming for it. Well,
is it is it neighbor or is it roommate?
Have you guys figured that out yet?
>> [laughter]
>> It's probably going to be neighbor.
We're going to get a house together.
Real good. CC, congratulations, man.
Welcome to New York. We can't wait to
see you up here and uh enjoy the rest of
your night. Thank you. Thank you.